Why is it beyond your scope of common sense that a candidate who does not meet the needs of the constituents they want votes from should shift to do so?
Why is that such an outlandish concept for you people?
They show up on the campaign trail and should be pushed to purpose by the people they are supposed to represent.
That is how this is supposed to work.
Instead, y'all are haranguing me, a U.S. citizen, for demanding a candidate for the U.S. Senate change her position on supporting a genocidal apartheid state that is literally stealing American taxpayer money.
Make it make sense, please!
We're going to fight the solidarity.
Listen to your people!
Because I hit hard.
Billionaires should be scared of.